<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Timeline on Product Designer, CDO at buzzvil</title>
    <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Timeline on Product Designer, CDO at buzzvil</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 11:07:21 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mmaxence.me/timeline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chief Design Officer @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/cdo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/cdo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was time to take a step back from product management and put a stronger focus on Design, as the team grew in numbers and our business now needs to better control our design outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 15:47:02 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-pm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From January 2021, I took on a product Manager role for our supply business. I led a cross-functional team of 10 members and I was in charge of the performance of our supply products interfaces (for App/Web Publishers) until March 2022. This was the first second-degree management opportunity I&amp;rsquo;ve had as this team also counts one PM in charge of specific products. After a little more than one year of kicking off this mission team, we&amp;rsquo;ve recorded several KPI improvements, with most products refactored for greater interconnection, paving the way for further opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Product Owner @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-po/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 15:47:02 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-po/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Since 2018 I&amp;rsquo;ve been facilitating amazing mission teams. The first mission was about giving the company a strong focus on improving our overall customer experience. This was a cross-disciplinary team and it happened right after our company moved to a matrix organization, adjusting our structure to accommodate the many newcomers and be more scalable.&#xA;Followed a couple of other close-ended missions I had the chance to initiate and complete, until late 2020.&#xA;These were priceless experiences that nurtured a strong interest in product growth, expanding the reach beyond product Design only. Life lessons really, learning through hit-and-miss experiences. Amazing opportunities to rinse &amp;amp; repeat my leadership and management processes throughout multiple, short experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head of Design @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-head-of-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/buzzvil-head-of-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alongside my current role as Product Manager, I lead a very compact and efficient team of rockstar designers. Considering my resources, I focused on building a very agile and autonomous Design work process based on high-quality hirings and autonomous workflows. All Designers are performing Peer reviews to promote feedback while all of us belong to different mission teams.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UX Design Lead @CMS Group</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/cms-lead-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/cms-lead-design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CMS group (previously 3S Informatique) offered me my first long projects. I spent more than 3 years working in research labs. I could adjust the methods I learned at school, learn how to interact inside a development team, and publish my very first research paper in Tokyo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Student &amp; Freelancer</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/freelance--school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2005 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/timeline/posts/freelance--school/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;head-full-of-dreams-and-a-true-passion-for-product-design&#34;&gt;Head full of dreams and a true passion for Product Design&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I graduated from the excellent &lt;a href=&#34;https://wwww.lecolededesign.com&#34;&gt;L&amp;rsquo;École de design Nantes Atlantique&lt;/a&gt; with a Master in Interaction Design with Honors.&#xA;I graduated from &lt;a href=&#34;https://artsetmetiers.fr/en&#34;&gt;L&amp;rsquo;École Normale Supérieure des Arts et Metiers&lt;/a&gt; with a Research Master in Virtual Reality &amp;amp; Innovation with honors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
