<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Chief Design Officer at buzzvil</title>
    <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Chief Design Officer at buzzvil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 15:47:02 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmaxence.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>High output management: identifying and measuring your design outputs</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/high_output_management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/high_output_management/</guid>
      <description>Design oriented Takeaways from Andrew Grove’s best seller. My CEO strongly recommended me to read “High output management” a while ago as my team was growing and my management responsibilities accentuated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tools to build a design system in 2020</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/tools_to_build_a_design_system_in_2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/tools_to_build_a_design_system_in_2020/</guid>
      <description>A snap taken during our last sprint prior to publish our system online
This is a healthy, yearly routine I genuinely recommend to follow regardless of the size of your team: gauging your current toolbox against what’s new in the busy design tool industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Tempo: the art of managing creative pace</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_tempo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 08:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_tempo/</guid>
      <description>Designers, like musicians, need to play in diapason in order to come up with melodious experiences. 🎶
This is a subjective essay, a short read about Creative team pace management. It is based on experience, discussions with peers over the years, personal thoughts &amp;amp; analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design criticism</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_criticism/</guid>
      <description>How to avoid friction when receiving feedback on your design. It usually starts like this:
 I don’t like the blue here, can you please change to something more&amp;hellip; red-ish?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study*(Designers&#43;Engineers)= ❤️ pt.2</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt2/</guid>
      <description>We’ve shared a first story about how we started a study between engineers and designers. The outcome was a lot of fun and a CI pipeline from Figma to Android environment called Phantom Box.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study*(Designers&#43;Engineers)= ❤️ pt.1</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt1/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago we started a small study group with engineers and designers to understand each other better. It was an insightful and fun experience. Fun enough to run 2 different projects summarized over 2 different stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design system at Buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-system-at-buzzvil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-system-at-buzzvil/</guid>
      <description>Design system vs startup. Takeaways.
We built a Design system. It took us time, resources and a lot of energy, involving pretty much everyone in our design team. And it’s just the beginning of a long story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design peer reviews to support our team growth</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-peer-reviews-to-support-our-team-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-peer-reviews-to-support-our-team-growth/</guid>
      <description>I always hope to see my teammates collaborate more. Now that we are at a stage of faster growth, more fellow designers are going to join us and it felt like a good timing to push forward this all peer-review strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buzzvil Design Team toolbox in 2019</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/buzzvil-design-team-toolbox-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/buzzvil-design-team-toolbox-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Max and I lead a team of designers at Buzzvil. When we’ve decided last year to drastically change our design toolbox, I was pleased to find plenty of insights from other teams around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
