<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Designer at buzzvil</title>
    <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Designer at buzzvil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 15:47:02 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mmaxence.me/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Design criticism</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_criticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design_criticism/</guid>
      <description>How to avoid friction when receiving feedback on your design. It usually starts like this:
 I don’t like the blue here, can you please change to something more&amp;hellip; red-ish?
 This is generally enough for a designer’s face to turn.. 😡 red-ish and internally blame the poor bastard’s parents for bringing him to this world. Probably also questioning why someone with such poor fashion taste would even dare question his or her Design choices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study*(Designers&#43;Engineers)= ❤️ pt.2</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt2/</guid>
      <description>We’ve shared a first story about how we started a study between engineers and designers. The outcome was a lot of fun and a CI pipeline from Figma to Android environment called Phantom Box. This story is about the second act of our study.
This time we’ve decided to pinpoint a problem within our company and try fixing it. It needed to be a small scale project just for us to be incubating the whole development process altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study*(Designers&#43;Engineers)= ❤️ pt.1</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/studydesigners&#43;engineers-%EF%B8%8F-pt1/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago we started a small study group with engineers and designers to understand each other better. It was an insightful and fun experience. Fun enough to run 2 different projects summarized over 2 different stories. Here is the first one, sharing both designer and engineer points of views.
At buzzvil we can freely start a study group, lunch being supported for the occasion. It was enough reason for us 5 to start questioning our workflow, 3 product designers and 2 engineers (client &amp;amp; devOps) on a weekly basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design system at Buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-system-at-buzzvil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-system-at-buzzvil/</guid>
      <description>Design system vs startup. Takeaways.
We built a Design system. It took us time, resources and a lot of energy, involving pretty much everyone in our design team. And it’s just the beginning of a long story. If you are working at a startup and are considering building a design system, you might find clues reading about our experience.
First off, we can’t ignore how time consuming building a system can be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design peer reviews to support our team growth</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-peer-reviews-to-support-our-team-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/design-peer-reviews-to-support-our-team-growth/</guid>
      <description>I always hope to see my teammates collaborate more. Now that we are at a stage of faster growth, more fellow designers are going to join us and it felt like a good timing to push forward this all peer-review strategy.
It’s never too late. We’ve been a team of 4 designers for the last 2 years, including 2 product / 2 visual designers. Collaboration &amp;amp; Review have been naturally there as soon as the team got 2 product designers, but it’s never been a thing across the entire team, probably due to the fact that some of our designers are working remotely, bringing communication issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buzzvil Design Team toolbox in 2019</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/buzzvil-design-team-toolbox-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/blog/posts/buzzvil-design-team-toolbox-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Max and I lead a team of designers at Buzzvil. When we’ve decided last year to drastically change our design toolbox, I was pleased to find plenty of insights from other teams around the world. This post talks about our decisions and related needs!
To give a quick background, we are a team of 5 designers located in Seoul and Taipei. The team counts 3 Product designers including myself and 2 visual - Brand designers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>