<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Experience on PO, Lead product Design at buzzvil</title>
    <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Experience on PO, Lead product Design at buzzvil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 15:47:02 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mmaxence.me/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Product Owner @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-po/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 15:47:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-po/</guid>
      <description>I recently took on a Product Owner role for our supply business. I handle a cross-disciplinary team of 8 members and I am in charge of the performances of our supply products (for App/Web Publishers). These new responsibilities came after a company-wide restructuring, aiming at being more performance-oriented as well as customer-obsessed. A great way for me to strengthen my business understanding and grow my management skills. I intentionally moved further away from product Design to better understand how product business works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-pm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 15:47:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-pm/</guid>
      <description>Since 2018 I&amp;rsquo;ve been leading amazing mission teams. The first mission was about giving the company a strong focus on improving our overall customer experience. This was a cross-disciplinary team and it happened right after our company moved to a matrix organization, adjusting our structure to accommodate the many newcomers and be more scalable. After that mission ended we merged with another mission to regroup and simplify our inventory and I took the lead to ease the transition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Head of Design @buzzvil</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-head-of-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2014 11:07:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/buzzvil-head-of-design/</guid>
      <description>New start, new challenges, new life In Late 2014 I joined buzzvil as the lead designer, a dynamic startup based in Seoul. In June I was releasing my first Android and iOS Honeyscreen App with buzzvil. This is the beginning of a long story during which I&amp;rsquo;ve already learned so much!
Work smarter, be lazier I don&amp;rsquo;t consider myself lazy per se, but I do enjoy a lot finding solutions to shorten boring, repetitive work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UX Design Lead @CMS Group</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/cms-lead-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2011 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/cms-lead-design/</guid>
      <description>CMS group (previously 3S Informatique) offered me my first long projects. I spent more than 3 years working on research-oriented projects. I could adjust the methods I learned at school, learn how to interact inside a development team, and publish my very first research paper in Tokyo.
The real test After taking 2 months break in Korea following my graduation, I started working for a Research Lab incubated by CMS Group, an IT consulting company based in Paris.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student &amp; Freelancer</title>
      <link>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/freelance-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2005 11:31:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mmaxence.me/experience/posts/freelance-school/</guid>
      <description>Head full of dreams and a true passion for Product Design I graduated from the excellent L&amp;rsquo;École de design Nantes Atlantique - Master in Interaction Design with Honors. I graduated from L&amp;rsquo;École Normale Supérieure des Arts et Metiers - Research Master in Virtual Reality &amp;amp; Innovation with honors.
 I got an amazing last year&amp;rsquo;s internship at a Parisian startup called Domolib&#39;, creating home automation systems. In 6 months I could see my very first iPad application being published with positive reviews.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
